Take a Walk - Passion Pit
这些地方
All these kinds of places
看起来有好些年头了
Make it seem like it's been ages
明天就有新的大楼
Tomorrow some new building
将触及天空
Will scrape the sky
我喜爱这个国家
I love this country dearly
我可以感受到
I can feel the ladder clearly
但我从没想过
But I never thought
我要孤单地去尝试
I'd be alone to try
一次我在宾夕法车站外
Once I was outside Penn Station
贩卖红色白色的康乃馨
Selling red and white carnations
我们还是孤单的，我的妻子跟我
We were still alone  my wife and I
在我们结婚前，要存钱
Before we married  saved my money
让我的妻子受不了了
Brought my dear wife over
现在我努力工作
Now I work to bring
为了把全家都带来
My family stateside
从他们住的船上下来
But off the boat they stayed
一会儿就要分散了
A while then scattered
穿过海滩
Across the coast
有一年我看到他们
Once a year I'll see them
几乎有一个礼拜
For a week or so at most
我去散个步
I take a walk
去散个步
Take a walk  take a walk
Take a walk
去散个步
Take a walk  take a walk
Take a walk
我去散个步
I take a walk
去散个步
Take a walk  take a walk
Take a walk
去散个步
实践并不是完美的
Practice isn't perfect
但是市场减少了损失
But the market cuts the loss
我提醒我自己
I remind myself that times
那个时候可能更糟
Could be much worse
我妻子并不问我问题
My wife won't ask me questions
也并没有那么多需要问
There's not so much to ask
她从不炫耀
And she'll never flaunt
当身边都是无形的压力时
Around an empty purse
有次我岳母来
Once my mother-in-law came
只是待几个晚上
Just to stay a couple nights
就决定她要留下来
Then decided she would stay
以度过余生
The rest of her life
我看着我的小孩
I watch my little children
在玩滑板游戏
Play some board game
在厨房里
In the kitchen
我坐下祈祷
And I sit and pray
他们不能感到我的惊恐
They never feel my strife
我的搭档过来说
But then my partner called to say
养老基金没有了
The pension funds were gone
我们的投资泡了汤
We made some bad investments
账户已经透支
Now the accounts are overdrawn
我去散个步
I take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
宝贝这是你儿子
Honey  it's your son
我想我欠得太多了
I think I borrowed just too much
我们有税，我们有账单
We had taxes  we had bills
我们的未来已经注定
We had a lifestyle to front
今天晚上我发誓
And tonight I swear
我会回家
I'll come home
我们会亲热
And we'll make love
像我们年轻的时候
Like we're young
明天你会做晚饭
And tomorrow you'll cook dinner
给邻居和他们的孩子
For the neighbors and their kids
我们可以分开这些社会主义者
We can rip apart those Socialists
撕开他们的税单
And all their damn taxes
不过我并不是罪犯
But see I am no criminal
我的两个膝盖都不好了
I'm down on both bad knees
我是一个不敢承诺的懦夫
I'm just too much a coward to admit
当我被需要
When I'm in need
我去散个步
I take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
Take a walk  take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk
I take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk  take a walk
Take a walk
我去散个步
Take a walk  take a walk
Take a walk